Victor Velasquez

Developer

Phone: 619-929-5760 **LinkedIn:** www.linkedin.com/in/victor-dev/

I am a developer in Las Vegas with a passion for learning and solving problems using creative solutions. I can work within strict usability guidelines, ensuring a positive user experience across multiple devices and screen sizes. I also have experience with Agile (Scrum) methodologies and using version control for build processes.

Technical Skills:

HTML5

• CSS3

JavaScript

React JS

MySQL

Node JS

Git

Babel

Express

• Unix Command

Line

Flexbox

Responsive Web

Design

React Native

Redux

Jquery

• Pivotal Tracker

Agile/Scrum

Semantic UI

Arduino

Raspberry Pi

IoT

Webpack

Experience:

• **PunchCode** *Coding Bootcamp Student* 5/2018 - Present 12-week intensive full stack web development training. The primary focus was on using JavaScript to build fully-functioning web applications using React JS.

Lyft Community Associate, Driver 3/2017 - 5/2018
 Managed day-to-day customer facing rental operations including new driver onboarding, existing driver support, and vehicle return processes. Also maintained excellent partner relationships (Hertz and Pep Boys) at the branch level.

• **Oto Float** Junior IT Technician, Junior Developer 6/2016 - 3/2017 Handled software and hardware installations (ex: Raspberry Pi, IoT, Arduino).

Lyynks QA Analyst
 Tested software and submitted detailed reports of bugs and issues using Pivotal Tracker.

Education:

PunchCode Certificate — Front-End Web Development 2018
 Platt College Bachelor of Science — Media Arts 2008 - 2011